<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Mark Kumar</title>
 <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/"/>
 <updated>2022-11-05T16:56:04+01:00</updated>
 <id>https://mk-unlimtied.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Mark</name>
   <email>marrkkumarr@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>A/B Testing Your Google Ads</title>
   <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/2020/07/31/ab-testing-ads"/>
   <updated>2020-07-31T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/2020/07/31/ab-testing-ads</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;To put on short sentences. A/B Testing is when you would need to test out if your ads are getting you the best conversion from your website or any ads for that matter on google platforms. This is similar to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://mk-unlimited.github.io/me/2017/01/02/quality-score-google-ads&quot;&gt;ads quality score&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.dmagency.us/wp-content/uploads/imagen-google-ads-768x512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;google ads experimenting&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you want to improve your Google Ads campaigns? Enter Google Ads Campaign Experiments, or ACE for short. ACE is a feature that helps you measure the impact of potential changes before applying them to a campaign. When used properly, it does this as a vehicle for A/B testing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we discussed in our previous post, A/B testing is essentially a process applying basic scientific principles to digital advertising. Following the first things we learned in elementary school science, this is achieved by comparing two versions of a campaign wherein all variables but one are controlled, and it’s the effect of this manipulated variable that’s being measured.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An A/B test begins by establishing a clear question and resulting objective that the test’s outcome should answer. For example, “Will a different landing page outperform the first landing page?” or “Will changes in the ad copy outperform the original ad copy?” Also important is establishing which key performance indicators (KPIs) you’ll use to determine the definition of “outperform.” Whichever KPIs you choose will depend what your objective is for this campaign — for example, a campaign trying to increase conversions would probably be primarily measuring, well, conversions, whereas a campaign trying to increase people’s awareness or consideration of a brand would be better served with a different KPI like impressions, clicks, site engagement, or numerous others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And again, the most important thing to remember: Other than the single manipulated one, control your variables!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-big-ol-guide-to-the-google-experiment-process--settings&quot;&gt;A Big Ol’ Guide to the Google Experiment Process &amp;amp; Settings&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.operationroi.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/Test-confidently-blog-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;experimenting google ads&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first part of beginning a Google Ads experiment is to create a draft. This is a duplication of a pre-existing campaign that allows you to easily make your variable change and submit as an experiment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After creating your draft and defining the manipulated variable, you’ll select your start and end date. Google recommends no shorter than four to six weeks for experiments testing bid strategy, since it takes the system a while to learn how to best optimize your bids. And even if you’re conducting an experiment based on creative factors like ad copy or image ads, it’s important to remember they must go through an approval period. Usually, that should take no longer than a day, but it’s worth factoring into the schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the start and end dates are determined, you’ll decide on your experiment split. This is where you define how the daily experiment budget will be split between the A and B variations. Per Google, it’s best to stick with a 50/50 budget split as the quickest way to achieve statistically significant results. Along with the budget split, there’s the split options to decide on. These options are search-based or cookie-based. Search-based experiments allow search queries to be evenly split between A/B variations. This carries the risk that a user sees both the A and B variations if they search for the terms multiple times, which could influence their behavior around one of the versions and make data less accurate. Cookie-based experiments, meanwhile, use your remarketing lists to prevent the same user from seeing both the A and B versions of your ad. Intuitively, this means the resulting data can be more accurate. Google generally recommends a cookie-based approach for this reason.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the campaign experiment and once it’s over, you’ll be able to view statistically significant data metrics at the top of the experiments campaign section. This way, you can gain an easy and accurate understanding of the performance of a campaign update.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;ways-to-experiment&quot;&gt;Ways to Experiment&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.stressfreeprint.co.uk/media/wysiwyg/Landing_Page_Plan_Printing_Detail.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ways to experiment with google ads&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to variables to test, there’s no “right” one. This is because different campaigns have different objectives and relative weaknesses upon which to be improved. There are, however, some common choices. Here are some of them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Testing bid strategy is where you control all the creative aspects so the ads appear and link to the same destination but are powered differently — for example, manual CPC versus target CPA. Like we mentioned earlier, bid strategy experiments require at least four to six weeks to see statistically significant results since the algorithm learning period takes time for Google Ads software to optimize bidding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Similarly, you can experiment with bid or scheduling adjustments. This is to find out if ad performance is affected by time-based or bidding factors. For example, what happens if you only run ads during a certain time of day, or bid higher for high-converting terms? These kind of variables are about determining how to use your input resources as efficiently as possible to decrease your cost per acquisition (or other cost rate metrics).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the likely first variables that come to mind are for creative variations. This can be a change in ad copy, imagery, or other visual factors. The reasoning behind this kind of experiment is pretty self-explanatory; will changing wording or other creative factors improve our campaign’s performance?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to creative variations in the ad itself is variations in landing pages. This isn’t actually about creative distinctions, but rather if linking an ad to a different established landing page leads to better results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly are changes to ad group structure, keywords, and match type. This is pretty straightforward; while your KPIs obviously would vary depending on your campaign objectives, whichever you choose can be measured in relation to new keywords, ad groupings, or match type variations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, running frequent campaign experiments will help you get the most out of them. They’re a good way of gaining valuable insight into how people engage (or don’t) with your digital advertising and give you a foundation on which to improve your performance. Successful online marketing is fueled by attentiveness and curiosity — A/B testing gives you a vessel to engage those attributes and subsequently get more out of your efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Quality Score Could Reduce Your PPC Cost</title>
   <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/2017/01/02/quality-score-google-ads"/>
   <updated>2017-01-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/2017/01/02/quality-score-google-ads</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.adsecure.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/image-adsecure-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;ad quality&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quality Score is a diagnostic tool meant to give you a sense of how well your ad quality compares to other advertisers. This score is measured on a scale from 1-10 and available at the keyword level. A higher Quality Score means that your ad and landing page are more relevant and useful to someone searching for your keyword, compared to other advertisers. You can use the Quality Score diagnostic tool to identify where it might be beneficial to improve your ads, landing pages, or keyword selection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quality Score is calculated based on the combined performance of 3 components:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
1. Expected clickthrough rate (CTR): The likelihood that your ad will be clicked when shown.
2. Ad relevance: How closely your ad matches the intent behind a user&apos;s search.
3. Landing page experience: How relevant and useful your landing page is to people who click your ad.

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-does-not-impact-ad-quality&quot;&gt;What does not impact ad quality&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to google ads documentation, we see that Frequency of ads, Bidding , Conversions reported and Account structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bidding: The amount you bid may affect your Ad Rank, but it doesn’t impact the assessment of your ad quality&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Account structure: Moving an ad group with the same ads and keywords to another campaign or account does not impact your ad quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Frequency of ads: How often your ads show is determined by your bids, budget, and keyword competition, but it does not affect your ad quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conversions reported: Your reported conversions do not impact your ad quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;ways-to-improve-ad-quality-score&quot;&gt;Ways to Improve Ad Quality Score&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quality Score can be a valuable tool in identifying ways to improve your ads, keywords, and landing pages. You can think of Quality Score as a general indicator of which areas to focus on to improve ad quality, rather than a score to be optimized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article guides you through different ways to use your Quality Score to improve your performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-review-your-quality-score-components&quot;&gt;1. Review your Quality Score components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For specific insights on where to make improvements, dive deeper into the 3 components of Quality Score as stated above:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;
 1. Expected clickthrough rate: The likelihood that your ad will be clicked when shown.
 2. Ad relevance: How closely your ad matches the intent behind a user&apos;s search.
 3. Landing page experience: How relevant and useful your landing page is to people who click your ad.
 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These components can help you see whether to update your ad text, keyword selection, or landing page content. You’ll see a status of “Below average,” “Average,” and “Above average” for each component to give you a sense of which areas might need improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key point is: give your users what they’re looking for and good performance should follow. Focus on your long-term performance goals and look for ways to reach them by improving your user experience, using Quality Score as a diagnostic tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-make-ads-more-relevant-to-keywords&quot;&gt;2. Make ads more relevant to keywords&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ad relevance shows you how relevant your ads are to the keywords they’re targeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.searchenginejournal.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/acf3fcff-f2d6-4cc4-b74d-389658ff34cd.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;ads relevance&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your Ad relevance has a status of “Below average” or “Average,” try these best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Match the language of your ad text more directly to user search terms.
Look for ad groups with many different keywords that can’t be easily addressed by the same ad. Split these ad groups into multiple ad groups that better match to the user’s searches.
Try grouping your keywords into themes to increase relevance. These themes can be based on your products, services, or other categories. For example, if you sell rings, you can have a group of keywords for “engagement rings” and another group of keywords for “wedding bands.”
Note that moving an ad group with the same ads and keywords to another campaign or account does not impact your ad quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-try-to-improve-your-clickthrough-rate-ctr&quot;&gt;3. Try to improve your clickthrough rate (CTR)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.goodfirms.co/images/click-through-rate-formula.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;click through rate&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expected clickthrough rate indicates how likely people are to click your ad. If your Exp. CTR has a status of “Below average” or “Average,” try these best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Edit your ad text to make your offer more compelling to your target audience.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ensure the details in your ad match the intent of your keywords.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Highlight a unique benefit of your product or service, such as free shipping.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experiment with different calls to action that connect closely with your landing page.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create compelling calls to action with words like “Buy, Sell, Order, Browse, Find, Sign up, Try, Get a Quote.”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Be more specific in your ad text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There may be times when a more specific ad leads to lower CTRs, but higher conversion rates. Look for the balance that leads to the best possible performance for your goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, let’s say you sell luxury dress shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding a phrase to your ad like “free bow tie with order” may attract shoppers looking for deals. On the other hand, phrases like “fine craftsmanship” or “custom Italian design” may engage people looking for a quality brand. This highly depends on who your targeting and the value your product provides. Due to this, the bargain message may get you more clicks, but may not result in as many loyal customers over the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-consider-updating-your-landing-page&quot;&gt;4. Consider updating your landing page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bringing people to your site is only one part of online marketing. It’s important to provide visitors with an excellent experience on your website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://unbounce.com/photos/750-X-400-2x.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;landing page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your Landing page exp. has a status of “Below average” or “Average,” try these best practices:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Give people what they’re looking for. If someone searches for “flannel shirts” and clicks your ad for “flannel shirts,” the landing page they go to should feature your flannel inventory.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Keep messaging consistent from ad to landing page. Make sure the page follows through on the ad’s offer or call to action. Even if you have no control over your site, you can still experiment to find the most useful existing pages.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Try using conversion rate as a proxy for good landing page experience. It doesn’t impact your landing page status, but it can be a good way for you to measure and optimize.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make your website mobile friendly. Ease of navigation is something users value even more on mobile websites. You can use the Mobile-Friendly Test to see how well your landing page works on mobile devices.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improve loading speed. The speed at which your page loads can be the difference between someone bouncing or buying.
Keep in mind, the word-for-word phrase from a search term doesn’t need to be on your landing page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A search for “South Chicago Chihuahua-friendly budget hotels” doesn’t need to lead to a landing page with the headline “South Chicago Chihuahua-friendly budget hotels.” Instead focus on creating great experiences that deliver what the user is looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-use-quality-score-with-other-metrics&quot;&gt;5. Use Quality Score with other metrics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look at other metrics in your account, like clickthrough rate, conversion rate, and site engagement. They’re connected to your performance and can help as you look for specific areas to improve. As you review your performance, you can use Quality Score as a filter to tell you where to focus your efforts:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Look through your high-performing keywords and use Quality Score to identify which ones may do even better with changes to your ads and landing pages.
Use low Quality Scores and component status to find weaker trends for ad relevance, clickthrough rate, and landing page experience that might exist across your account, and set long-term plans for improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>LPI and Examples</title>
   <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/2016/11/27/lpi-examples"/>
   <updated>2016-11-27T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
   <id>https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/2016/11/27/lpi-examples</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;low-purchase-intent-lpi-search-terms&quot;&gt;Low Purchase Intent (LPI) Search Terms&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Negative keywords are words and phrases that you do not want searchers to associate with your products and services (see Google Ads blog for some high-level information about negative keywords). When you add negative keywords to your PPC campaigns your ads will not be served if those words are part of the user’s search query.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-would-this-be-important-&quot;&gt;Why would this be important ?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Low Purchase Intent Search Terms are keywords that do not work with a specific industry or brand. The reason this listing words that are negative and do not works is because it gets rid of the majority of this “low purchase intent” (LPI) searches — searches for terms that are conceptually related to your root keyword, but have little or no drive to actually buy your insurance product or service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These LPI searches can be confusing — many of them may actually increase CTR because of their informational nature (people are more likely to click the first ad they see if they’re just hunting for data), but they’ll almost always decrease the one thing you really care about: your conversion rate. My advice? Get rid of them as soon as possible to decrease ad spend. Clicks don’t make you money. Conversions do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are 301 negative keywords for your insurance company’s Google Ads campaign from this &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@nicksaraev/insurance-company-google-ads-the-301-best-negative-keywords-for-your-insurance-company-google-ads-4e0aa3f01fe5&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; 
 “act of”

“advisory”

“app”

“apps”

“architecture”

“arena”

“article”

“articles”

“associations”

“bank”

“blog”

“blogs”

“book”

“books”

“bulletin”

“bulletins”

“burn”

“burner”

“calculator”

“careers”

“case studies”

“case study”

“casual encounters”

“cd”

“certification”

“certifications”

“channel”

“cheap”

“cheapest”

“chicks”

“class”

“classes”

“clearance”

“close out”

“close outs”

“closeout”

“closeouts”

“club”

“clubs”

“code”

“college”

“colleges”

“community”

“compliance”

“condo”

“conference”

“conferences”

“council”

“councils”

“county court”

“course”

“courses”

“crafts”

“create”

“creating”

“curriculum vitae”

“CV”

“data”

“dating”

“define”

“definition”

“desktop”

“developer”

“developers”

“diagram”

“discount”

“discounted”

“disk”

“diy”

“do it yourself”

“download”

“downloads”

“dvd”

“ebay”

“education”

“employer”

“employers”

“employment”

“error”

“exam”

“example”

“examples”

“exams”

“facebook”

“FAQ”

“festival”

“file”

“files”

“films”

“forum”

“forums”

“free”

“freeware”

“full time”

“game”

“games”

“gnu”

“graphic”

“graphics”

“guide”

“guides”

“gulf”

“hack”

“hacks”

“hand made”

“handmade”

“hire”

“hiring”

“history”

“home”

“homemade”

“homes”

“how can I”

“how can”

“how do I”

“how does”

“how to”

“icon”

“icons”

“image”

“images”

“income”

“inexpensive”

“info”

“information”

“institute”

“institutes”

“instructor”

“instructors”

“intern”

“interns”

“internship”

“internships”

“j-peg”

“j-pegs”

“job opening”

“job openings”

“job”

“jobs”

“journal”

“journals”

“jpeg”

“jpegs”

“jpg’s”

“jpg”

“kinky”

“law”

“learn about”

“libraries”

“library”

“liquidation”

“logo”

“logos”

“looking for work”

“low cost”

“lyric”

“lyrics”

“magazine”

“magazines”

“make”

“making”

“map”

“maps”

“meaning of”

“metrics”

“microsoft”

“music video”

“music”

“naked”

“new hires”

“news”

“newsletter”

“newsletters”

“newspaper”

“newspapers”

“nude”

“occupation”

“occupations”

“odd lots”

“open source”

“opening”

“openings”

“opportunities”

“opportunity”

“overstock”

“part time”

“pdf”

“pdfs”

“personals”

“photo”

“photograph”

“photographs”

“photos”

“pics”

“picture”

“pictures”

“pinterest”

“pix”

“police”

“porn”

“porno”

“price”

“prices”

“pricing”

“program”

“programs”

“public domain”

“quote”

“quotes”

“real estate”

“recruiter”

“recruiters”

“recruiting”

“recruitment”

“remainder”

“remainders”

“report”

“reports”

“research”

“resource”

“resources”

“resume”

“resumes”

“retail”

“retailer”

“retailers”

“review”

“reviews”

“ringtones”

“salaries”

“salary”

“sample”

“samples”

“school”

“schools”

“seminar”

“seminars”

“sex”

“shareware”

“short cut”

“short cuts”

“shortcut”

“shortcuts”

“snapchat”

“soft ware”

“software”

“statistics”

“stats”

“student”

“success stories”

“success story”

“teacher”

“teachers”

“template”

“templates”

“textbook”

“textbooks”

“theories”

“theory”

“tip”

“tips”

“torrent”

“torrents”

“trail”

“training”

“tutor”

“tutorial”

“tutorials”

“tutors”

“twitter”

“universities”

“university”

“utube”

“video”

“weather”

“what are”

“what i”

“what is”

“when can”

“when i”

“where can”

“white paper”

“white papers”

“wiki”

“wikipedia”

“windows 10”

“windows 2000”

“windows 7”

“windows 8.1”

“windows 8”

“windows xp”

“windows”

“wix”

“wordpress”

“work”

“workshop”

“workshops”

“x-rated”

“xxx”

“youtube”

&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;other-examples&quot;&gt;Other Examples&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is another example if your looking to remove bargain hunter for clicking your ads. Which will cost you money. These negative keywords will help if you are positioned as a premium provider. If you do want visitors for these keyword concepts, create an additional campaign or ad group to focus on these discount concepts, and specifically bid on keywords that contain these words. And then make sure to add this list of negative keywords to the campaigns or ad groups that do not target the discount audience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot;bargain&quot;

&quot;cheap&quot;

&quot;clearance&quot;

&quot;close out&quot;

&quot;close outs&quot;

&quot;closeout&quot;

&quot;closeouts&quot;

&quot;coupon&quot;

&quot;coupon code&quot;

&quot;discount&quot;

&quot;discounted&quot;

&quot;free&quot;

&quot;inexpensive&quot;

&quot;liquidation&quot;

&quot;odd lots&quot;

&quot;overstock&quot;

&quot;remainder&quot;

&quot;remainders&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking at this method of looking what not to include rather than what to include may help you achieve better results in  your ppc ads.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Visuals for Google Ads ?</title>
   <link href="https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/me/2014/05/12/visuals-for-googleads"/>
   <updated>2014-05-12T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
   <id>https://mk-unlimtied.github.io/2014/05/12/visuals-for-googleads</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I start of with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.krusecontrolinc.com/rule-of-7-how-social-media-crushes-old-school-marketing-2021/&quot;&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; that was done a while back that states you’ll come into contact with that prospect at least 7 times just to create interest or to be heard by the prospect. Not all touches are good, some may be bad or good. The point is that you’ll need to make the message meaningful and not regular sales talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With competitors like tiktok using more and more visuals that captures peoples attention in a short amount of time. Google is starting to make is products more visually appealing. Just take a look at what Google’s VP said in this &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2022/07/12/google-exec-suggests-instagram-and-tiktok-are-eating-into-googles-core-products-search-and-maps/&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;. Since younger audiences tend to crave more visually rich content, it would be wise to incoporate visual elements in your advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;“In our studies, something like almost 40% of young people, when they’re looking for a place for lunch, they don’t go to Google Maps or Search,” he continued. “They go to TikTok or Instagram.” - Google&apos;s VP
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventhough Google is looking to incoporate AR into it’s search function to enhance engagement. There are ways such as google ads display and youtube ads which help act as a supporting tool or a build up to that final purchase. That is where search ads becomes the final part of the process for your poe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Landmarks_Live_View.gif&quot; alt=&quot;google_live_view&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to distribute content with rich in visual content as of 2022&lt;br /&gt;
Always use high quality images&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
